# **BHAVIK GILBERT**

Software Engineer

bhaviklob@hotmail.com

**+**447405805628

**Bhavik Gilbert** 

Bhavik-Gilbert

Portfolio Website

### **EDUCATION**

Computer Science BSc (Hons)



King's College London

2021 - 2024

CS50 Online



Harvard University

2022

#### A-Levels

Mathematics, Computer Science Physics, Economics



Leyton VI Form College

2019 - 2021

### **SKILLS**

- Python
- □ □ HTML/XML/CSS
- j Javascript (React/Threejs)
- PHP
- ② ③ ⑤ C/C++/C#
- **5** Scala

### INTERESTS

- Volleyball
- Badminton
- Travel

#### REFERENCES

• dwin.nganga@leyton.ac.uk

#### **PROFILE**

Driven by an avid interest in Tech, I've come across a range of experiences in several positions within different sectors to help expand my knowledge, trying to find my footholds within the industry. To this end, I've dabbled in several fields: data analysis, game development, machine learning, web development and database systems.

Proceeding forward, I want to further develop my knowledge around the field of computer software outside the reach of personal projects, providing a tangible output into the industry, and bettering my problem-solving and algorithmic thinking in the process.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Location Camp Support Assistant**



#### **Funtech**

July 2022 - August 2022

- Managing and supporting tutors across 7 on-site locations to cultivate a safe and encouraging environment for learning
- Provided technical/IT/teaching support across courses, maintaining safeguarding standards, liaising with tutors and talking to clients and troubleshooting issues of all natures as they come up
- 3D Game Development(Unreal Engine), CyberSecurity(Kali Linux), Python(Basic/OOP/Pygame Development/AIML), Touch Typing, Roblox Development, Minecraft(Mods/Redstone) Development, Lego Robotics, Java(Basic)

## Computer Science Mentor



# Leyton VI Form College

September 2021 - October 2022

- Advising students in all aspects of their coursework, ranging from usage in PHP, JavaScript, SQL, C# and Python
- Teaching students to design and document systems during the development process
- Technologies focusing on web development, database systems, unity 3D game development, python 2D game development and AI development

### Computer Science Teacher



# Funtech

July 2021 - August 2021

- Taught classes of up to 6 ranged from 6 16 years in age
- Lego Robotics, 3D Game Development (Unreal Engine), CyberSecurity (Kali Linux), Python(OOP/Tensorflow AIML)

### **PROJECTS**

# **Property Portfolio Viewer Application**

### **Group Project - 4 Contributors**

- Java GUI Application(JavaFx, WebView)
- Application to allow users to view airbnb properties, get information about them and their location such as crime rate, transport links and average price point.

# Facial Recognition Login System

### Solo Project - 1 Contributor

- Python AI & SQL Database(Tkinter/PIL/CV2/DeepFace)
- Login system to use facial recognition in place of passwords, validiating and storing blob images on each successful login to improve the accuracy of the system overtime

# Photography Booking & Management System

#### Solo Project - 1 Contributor

- PHP/Javascript Web Development Database Booking System
- Booking system to allow clients to hire photographers alongside enable admin to effectively manage sales and view progress

Visit my portfolio website for more information